{
    "subject": "resource/For_Them_That_Trespass",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "For Them That Trespass is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8976660966873169,
            "question": "Is 'For Them That Trespass' a documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7671800851821899,
            "question": "Who directed 'For Them That Trespass'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7590768337249756,
            "question": "Can you name another film in the same genre as 'For Them That Trespass'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7453280687332153,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'For Them That Trespass'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7123914957046509,
            "question": "What makes 'For Them That Trespass' unique compared to other films in its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6766215562820435,
            "question": "What genre is 'For Them That Trespass'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4275375306606293,
            "question": "Where can I watch 'For Them That Trespass'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40543001890182495,
            "question": "When was 'For Them That Trespass' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40186065435409546,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with 'For Them That Trespass'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.203543558716774,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films of this type?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=For Them That Trespass is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7426_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with 'For Them That Trespass'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7426_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'For Them That Trespass' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7426_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch 'For Them That Trespass'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7426_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7426_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7426/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt states that Walter Hill's film Trespass is an action powerhouse, which is a type of film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n**Explanation:** The document titled \"For Them That Trespass (British Pathe 1947)\" and another one mentioning the same title describe it as an English writer-novelist melodrama, indicating that \"For Them That Trespass\" is indeed a film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}